Guide to the Yale College Records Concerning the Floating Counselor Program
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale College records concerning the floating counselor program
1974-1984
RU 576
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.75
(2 boxes)
The records consist of budget materials, applications, assignments and schedules, and statements documenting the Yale College floating counselor program.
Yale College (1887- )
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 9-E (YRG 9-E), Records of Yale College offices, programs, and projects.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of budget materials, applications, assignments and schedules, and statements documenting the Yale College floating counselor program.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by subject.
Peer counseling of students; Yale College (1887- )
- Records concerning the floating counselor program, 1974-1984; Accession 1988-A-016
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2021.
  - Floating Counselor Program
    - Applicants, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    - Selection material, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - PROP operations Planning/Administration, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Information, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Administrative matters, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Selection material, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Alternates, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Applicants, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Administrative matters, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Administration/Budget, 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12-19)
    - Selection material, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Alternates, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Applicants, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 22-29)
    - Assignments and schedules, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Financial Records
    - Budget, undergraduate affairs, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 32-38)
    - Organizations Budget, undergraduate, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Stock 6 supplies, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Yale Symphony 671C-32-00001, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Reimbursments, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Material checked to monthly statement, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 43-44)
    - Material to check, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Paid bills, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - General (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Budgets, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 48-49)
    - General appropriations, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Budgets, 1981-1981 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Organization budgets, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 52-53)
    - General, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 54-55)
    - Check requests and other charges, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 56-57)
    - Debate Team, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Yale Student Art Society, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Yale Dramat, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Minority Allied Health Organization, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Minority Business Associations, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 62-63)
    - Miscellaneous Department Accounts Special Use Accounts, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 64-66)
    - Yale Band, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Yale Dancers, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Black Pre-Law Society, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Black Undergraduate Women's Group, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 70-71)
    - Chess Club Gifts, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Despierta Boricua statements, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Gay Students Center, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Interminority Action Coalition, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Joint Council of Social Chairmen (JCSC), 1978-1984 (Box 2, Folder 76-81)
    - MECHA statements, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 82-83)
    - Women's Caucus, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 84-85)
    - Student-to-Student Counseling, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 86-87)
    - Leonardo da Vinci Society, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 88-89)
    - General, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 90)